Biographical files (UCLA University Archives Reference Collection). 1882- UARC.0745
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Biographical Files - Photographs., 1882-; Series 2.
  - MacQueen, James., b. 1929.
  - Madden, [ ? ].
  - Magoun, Horace Winchell., b.1907 - d.1991 Mar. 6
  - Mahler, Anna.
  - Mallon, Marguerite.
  - Malone, Gertrude.
  - Manning, Don., n.d.
  - Mansfield, Harold.
  - Marrocco, W. Thomas.
  - Mason, W.E.
  - Mathis, Judge.
  - Matsumura, Ella Mae., b. 1952.
  - Mattern, Marion.
  - Maverick, Lewis A.
  - Maxwell, Olga.
  - Mayers, David., b. 1936.
  - McAteer, Tim., n.d.
  - McBride, George M.
  - McBride, George McCutchen., b.1876 October 11 - d.1971 October 7
  - McClellan, Myrta.
  - McCluskey, F. Dean.
  - McCormick, Mona., b.1930 - d.1994 June 30
  - McCullough, James Douglas., b.1905 May 17 - d.1985 January 28
  - McCutchan, Joseph W., b.1917 December 24 - d.1982 October 15
  - McDonald, [ ? ].
  - McDonough, John J.
  - McFadden, [ ? ].
  - McIntosh, Doug.
    Men's basketball, 1964-1965.
  - McIntosh, Douglas.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1964, 1965, 1966.
  - McKenzie, Harriett.
  - McKenzie, Roderick.
  - McKinley, Arthur Patch.
  - McKinnon, D.S.
  - McLaughlin, Katherine.
  - McLean, Ephraim R., b. 1936.
  - McManus, George Stewart., b.1886-
  - McManus, Regina.
  - McMillan, William George, Jr., 1919-2002
  - McNeil, Robert J.
  - McNulty, [ ? ].
  - McPhail, Annie.
  - McWinney, William H.
  - Melkanof, [ ? ].
  - Meriam, J.L.
  - Merrill, Robert Valentine.
    UCLA Professor French Department.
  - Meyers, Frederic., b. 1917 - d. 1999.
  - Michaelis, Helen., color slides
    Curator, Rock Art Collection. UCLA Institute of Archaeology.
  - Miles, Paul.
  - Miller, Bruce.
  - Miller, Clinton E.
  - Miller, Earl J.
  - Miller, Gardner.
  - Miller, Hugh.
  - Miller, James.
  - Miller, Kent., 1960
  - Miller, Loye Holmes.
  - Miller, Norman P.
  - Miller, Pierre A.
  - Millspaugh, Jessie F.
  - Mink, James Valentine., b.1923-
    Includes 1966 image of Adelaide Tussler Schippers, Don Schippers, and James Mink planning first [national?] Oral History Colloquium (Oak Creek Canyon, New Mexico).
  - Mitchell, Daniel J. B.
  - Mitchell-Kernan, Claudia.
  - Mittelbach, Frank G., b. 1924.
  - Mitoma, Judy.
  - Modry, Southard.
  - Moore, Ernest Carroll.
  - Moore, Everett T.
  - Moore, Jean Macalister., b.1907 - 2001 August 21
  - Moore, Kate Gordon.
  - Moore, W.T.
  - Morgan, J.D.
  - Morgan, J.D. (UCLA 1941), b.1919 - d.1980 December 16
  - Morrison, Donald.
  - Morton, William S.
  - Moser, Marian (UCLA 1948).
    SEE: Commencement, 1948. (Photograph Collection)
  - Muller, Steven (UCLA 1948).
    President of the Johns Hopkins University, 1972-1990.
  - Mulloy, William J.
  - Murphy, Franklin David., b. 1916 jan 29 - d.1994 jun 16
  - Murphy, Judith (Mrs. Franklin D.)
  - Murray, James.
  - Murray, William E.
  - Naden, Kenneth.
  - Nakamoto, Kent., b. 1952.
  - Nehru, Jawaharlal., 1961 November
    India Prime Minister Jawaharlal Nehru visited UCLA in 1961 November 14.
  - Neiburger, Morris.
  - Neutra, Richard.
    Includes photographs of Richard Neutra and UCLA Chancellor Raymond B. Allen.
    Los Angeles-based architect.
  - Newcomer, Victor D., b.1916 April 5 - d.2002 March 15
  - Neylan, John Francis.
  - Nicklin, Peter.
  - Nixon, Charles Robert., b.1917 August 9
  - Nofziger, Edward C. (UCLA 1936)
  - Noga, Michael.
  - Norsworthy, Stan.
  - Nostrand, Richard.
  - Nunis, Doyce B., Jr.
  - O'Donnell, Cyril J., b. 1900 - d. 1976.
  - Ogden, [ ? ].
  - Ohen, Don.
  - O'Leary, Agnes.
  - O'Leary, Prentice., 1963
  - Olsen?
  - Orbach, Raymond.
  - Orfield, Gary.
  - Osborne, Alfred E. Jr., b. 1944.
  - Osuga, William.
  - Ouchi, William G., b. 1943.
  - Pagen, William.
  - Paige, Lowell.
  - Paine, Thomas O.
  - Palmer, [ ? ].
  - Parish, John Carl.
  - Park, Donald K.
  - Park, Rosemary.
  - Patterson, Steve., n.d.
  - Pauley, Edwin W.
  - Pecsok, R.L.
  - Pederson, Jay.
  - Pegrum, Dudley.
  - Perkins, Rollin M.
  - Perloff, Harvey.
  - Petit, Roger.
  - Phelps, Waldo Woodson., b.1918 June 15 - d.2004 Jan 31
    UCLA Professor of Rhetoric (Dept. of English); instrumental in the founding of the Dept. of Speech and served as chair (1964-1971).
  - Phillips, Robert.
  - Pierskalla, William., b. 1934.
  - Pillsbury, A.F.
  - Plough, Estella.
  - Plunkett, O.A.
  - Popenoe, Wilson.
  - Popper, Jan.
  - Postley, John.
  - Postley, Judy Colyer (UCLA 1945)
  - Pound, Roscoe.
  - Powell, Alan.
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark., b.1906 September 3 - d.2001 March 14
  - Png, Ivan P. L., b. 1957.
  - Prasow, Paul., b. 1915 - d. 1982.
  - Preston, James.
  - Profit, Mel., 1962
  - Prothro, J. Thompson "Tommy."
    UCLA football coach, 1965-1970.
  - Prothro, Tommy., n.d.
  - Puckett, William.
  - Purdy, Rick., n.d.
  - Putnam, William C.
    UCLA Faculty - Geology.
  - Rada, Edward Louis., 1916-2005
  - Raia, Anthony P., b. 1928 - d. 2012.
  - Rajaram, Kumar.
  - Ralston, Lee W.
  - Ramsey, James Blaine., b.1892 April 20 - d.1965 October 16
  - Reagan, Ronald.
  - Rees, John David.
  - Regents.
  - Richardson, John., 1964
  - Richardson, Leon J.
  - Richman, Barry., d. 1978.
  - Rieber, Charles Henry., b.1966 - d.1948
  - Ringer, Lee.
  - Robbins, George W., b. 1905 - d. 1994.
  - Roberts, Bessie.
  - Roberts, Jim.
  - Robinson, Jack Roosevelt (Jackie)., b.1919 - d.1972
  - Robson, J. Wesley.
  - Rodgers, Frank "Pepper."
  - Rogers, Bob.
  - Rolfe, Franklin P.
  - Roll, Richard W.
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor.
  - Roper, Hugh Trevor.
  - Rose, Frances E.
  - Rose, John.
  - ROTC.
  - Rouch, Jane.
  - Rowe, Curtis., n.d.
  - Royce, Josiah.
  - Rubel, John H.
  - Rubsamen, Walter H.
  - Rumelt, Richard P.
  - Russell, Richard.
  - Sakakibara, Mariko.
  - Salisbury, Ethel.
  - Salle, Anthony.
  - Salveson, M.
  - Sanders, Cora E.
    First Librarian (curator) of the William Andrews Clark Memorial Library.
  - Sanders, Henry R. "Red."
  - Sanders, Henry Russell.
  - Saner, Neville.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1967, 1968.
  - Santa Clara, Perdo.
  - Sarin, Rakesh K.
  - Sarnat, Bernard G., b.1912 September 1
    Includes selected images from the UCLA School of Dentristry's Bernard G. Sarnat International Lectureship In Bone Biology.
  - Sawhill, Clarence.
  - Saxon, David.
  - Sayles, Edward M.
  - Schifrin, Lalo.
  - Schmidt, Robert.
  - Schoenberg, Arnold.
  - Schollhammer, Hans.
  - Schomaker, C.B.
  - Schottland, Charles.
  - Schreiner, Alexander.
    UCLA organist (1930-1939); later became principal organist for the Mormon Tabernacle.
  - Schultz, David (Dave).
    Includes photograph taken during 1984 Olympics (Los Angeles) wrestling 75 kg. weight division.
  - Schultz, Edith.
  - Schwartz, Eduardo S.
  - Schwartz, Murray L.
  - Scothorn, Carol.
  - Scott, Carol Ann.
  - Scott, Flora Murray.
  - Seaman, Josephine E.
    Los Angeles State Normal School (LASNS) instructor of grammar and word analysis.
  - Sebo, Laurie.
  - See, Elliot.
  - Segel, Pearl.
  - Selznick, [ ? ].
  - Shaw, Charles E.
  - Sheats, Paul H., b.1907
    UCLA Professor of Education; Dean, University Extension.
  - Shelton, Cynthia.
  - Sherwood, Foster.
  - Sherwood, G.E.
  - Shneidman, Edwin S. (UCLA 1938, M.A. 1940), b.1918 May 13 - d.2009 May
  - Simons, Harry.
  - Sindell, Steve., 1963
  - Skinner, Carl.
  - Slagle, Larry., 1966
  - Slaughter, Fred.
  - Slichter, Louis B.
  - Slichter, Louis Byrne., b.1896-d.1978
    UCLA Emeritus Professor of Geophysics; Director, UCLA Instiute of Geophysics; UC Thirty-eighth Annual Faculty Lecturer (1963).
  - Smirnoff, [ ? ].
  - Smith, James.
  - Smith, Keith V., b. 1937 - d. 2011.
  - Smith, Laura.
  - Smith, Lawrence.
  - Smith, Page. [Charles Page Smith], b.1917-d.1995
    UCLA History faculty (1952-1964); founding Provost of Cowell College, University of California, Santa Cruz (1964).
  - Smith, W.S.
  - Smith, William A.
  - Smith, William French.
  - Smith, Wilbur J. (Jordan)
  - Sognnaes, R.F.
  - Solari, Al., 1942?
  - Sood, Sanjay.
  - Soper, E.K.
  - Soto, Raymond.
    2002 August 2 retirement party photographs.
  - Sowers, J.K.
  - Spaulding, William.
  - Spencer, Joseph.
  - Spender, John-Christopher., b. 1936.
  - Speroni, Charles., b.1911 - d.1984
  - Spiegel, Irving.
  - Splansky, Joel.
  - Spousler, O.L.
  - Sprong, David Henry, Jr.
  - Sproul, Ida W. (Mrs. Robert Gordon Sproul)
  - Sproul, Robert Gordon.
  - Sprowls, R. Clay., b. 1921 - d. 2010.
  - Stamp, Dudley L.S.E.
  - Stanley, Raymond.
  - Stark-Cavette, Nola.
  - Starr, Chauncey.
  - Stead, Tom.
  - Stein, Jules.
  - Steiner, George A., b. 1912.
  - Stevenson, Adlai.
  - Stewart, F.M.
  - Stockwell, Marvel.
  - Stoddard, A.J.
  - Stone, Hosmer W.
  - Stoutemyer, V.T.
  - Strauss, Lewis L.
  - Stravinsky, Igor.
  - Strode, Woodrow Wilson Woolwine "Woody" (UCLA attended 1936/37-1939/40)., b.1914 July 25 - d.1994 December 31
  - Subrahmanyam, Avanidhar.
  - Suits, Peter.
  - Sullivan, Ellen.
  - Sumner, Anne (UCLA 1926)., b.1904 July - d.2008 February 9
  - Sussman, Eric.
  - Sutherland, Gene.
  - Svenson, Elvin V.
  - Svenson, Elwin Victor., b.1926 February 12
  - Swami, Sri Ratnam.
  - Swanson, E. Burton.
  - Swedenberg, Hugh.
  - Tabush, Victor C.
  - Tacionis, [ ? ].
  - Takizawa, Bill Hideaki.
  - Tang, Sui (Chris).
  - Tannenbaum, Robert., b. 1915 - d. 2003.
  - Taylor, Craig.
  - Templin, E.K.
  - Terasaki, Paul I.
    UCLA Professor of Surgery.
  - Terza, Dante D.
  - Thomas, Evalyn Ann., b.1870 - d.1950
  - Thomas, Terry.
  - Thompson, Helen B.
  - Thompson, Orsie M.
  - Thorne-Rider, Sir Frederick.
  - Thornton, Margaret.
  - Tidball, Jack., c.1933
    Player on UCLA Men's Tennis team.
  - Tiselius, A.
  - Titman, Sheridan D., b. 1954.
  - Titus, C.H.
  - Topping, [ ? ].
  - Torous, Walter N.
  - Toure, Sekou.
  - Townsend, Colleen.
  - Tribus, Myron.
  - Troll, Carl.
  - Trope Lewis, Rosalee Diane (UCLA 1942).
    Rosalee Diane Trope was college poet laureate of California. SEE ALSO: Lewis, Benjamin G.
  - Trueblood, Kenneth.
  - Truman, Harry.
  - Turner, Justin G.
  - Turner, Ralph H.
  - Turner, Robert.
  - Tyler, Louise L., d.2004
  - Tyler, Randy., 1971
  - Uhlendorf, Bernard.
  - Underhill, Robert.
  - Underwood, Herbert W.
  - Ungerleider, J. Thomas.
  - Upham, J.S.
  - Valentine, Fred A.
  - Vallely, John., n.d.
  - Van Vliet, Robert C., Jr.
  - Varney, Burton.
  - Veatch, H.W.
  - Verger, Morris D.
  - Vernoy, Terry., 1971
  - Vijayaraghavan, P.K.
  - Von Grunebaum, Giselle. (Mrs. Gustav E. von Grunebaum)
  - Vosper, Robert Gordon., b.1913-d.1994
  - Waddell, Charles W.
  - Wagner, Roger.
  - Waite, Robert.
  - Walker, John., 1963
  - Walker, Melville.
  - Wallace, E.C.
  - Wallace, W.P.
  - Warner, A.H.
  - Warren, Edgar.
  - Warren, Michael.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1966, 1967, 1968.
  - Warren, Mrs. Stafford L.
  - Warren, Stafford Leak., b.1896 - d.1981
  - Washington, Kenneth "Kenny" Stanley (UCLA 1941)., b.1918 August 31 - d.1971 June 24
  - Watts, Alan.
  - Waxman, Franz.
  - Webber, H.J.
  - Webster, Lloyd E.
  - Weicker, Steve.
  - Weil, Leonard.
  - Weinstein, Saul.
  - Welch, Ivo.
  - Welch, Jay (UCLA 19--).
    SEE ALSO: Royce Hall. organ (Photogaph Files)
  - Wellman, Paul.
  - Westergaard, Waldemar.
  - Weston, J. Frederick., b. 1916 - d. 2009.
  - Westra, Dorothy.
  - Wheeler, Benjamin Ide.
  - White, Eric Wyndham.
  - White, Howard.
  - White, Johnny., 1963
  - Whitice, Belle H.
  - Whymont, William.
  - Widmer, Don., 1967
  - Wildman, Samuel G.
  - Williams, D.C.
  - Williams, Gordon R.
  - Williams, Harold M., b. 1928.
  - Williams, Robert., b. 1913 - d. 2001.
  - Willison, Bruce G.
  - Wilson, Charles Z., Jr.
  - Wilson, Florence.
  - Wilson, Howard E.
  - Wilson, James Q., b. 1931 - d. 2012.
  - Wilt, [ ? ].
  - Winstein, Saul., d.1969
  - Winter, William.
  - Winters, Grace E.
  - Witcher, Dick., 1964
  - With, Karl Eberhard., b.1891 - d.1980
  - Wittenborg, Karin.
  - Wolf, Cheryl.
  - Wolf, Lulu.
  - Wolpert, Julian.
  - Wooden, John.
  - Woodridge, "Virginia."
  - Woodworth, Dorothy.
  - Worthington, E.R.
  - Wright, Frances.
  - Wright, Kenneth.
  - Wyle, D.C.
  - Yeargain, Eloisa.
  - Yoshino, Michael Y.
  - Yost, S. William.
  - Young, Charles Edward., b.1931 December 30 -
  - Young, Nona.
  - Young, Sue K., b.1932 - d.2001
  - Young, William G.
  - Zeidberg, David.
  - Zeitlin, Jake.
  - Zener, [ ? ].
  - Zeno, Larry., 1963, n.d.
  - Zhang, Shi.
  - Zierer, Clifford.
  - Zierer, Paul.
  - Zorn, Max.
  - Zumeta, William M., b. 1947.
  - Zweers, John.